ARIF BABAYEV

Baku, Azerbaijan +994774407050

arifrb@code.edu.az Linkedin Portfolio Github

.NET & React developer with 5 months of experience. ASP.NET MVC, RestAPI, and client-side web development expertise. Worked on several projects for multiple clients, including implementing .Net Framework to .Net Core, several services in .Net 6, handling SOAP services to RestAPI project, multilayered patterns, multi-tier architectures, continuous integration, and continuous deployment.

EXPERIENCE

JULY 2023 – PRESENT BACKEND DEVELOPER, YapıKredi Bank

- Maintained existing software applications by fixing bugs
- Fixing customer problems on SQL and add new features to Asp.NET App

MAY 2023 – PRESENT FRONTEND DEVELOPER, ISU STARTUP

- Developing UI of application
- Updating design elements, and adding new features.

AUG 2022 - JAN 2023

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER, GOLFHEAP COMPANY

- •Involved in the entire product development lifecycle including the design, development, deployment
- Maintenance of new and existing features.

EDUCATION

2022-PRESENT

BACHELOR DEGREE, AZERBAIJAN STATE OIL AND INDUSTRY UNIVERSITY

03.2022 - 08.2022

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP, CODE ACADEMY AZERBAIJAN

SKILLS

- C#
- Restful API
- NodeJS
- Javascript React, TypeScript
- Back-End and Database Skills

- .NET Framework
- Databases: SQL Server, MongoDB
- Responsive Web Design
- Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS, SCSS

Soft Skills

- Dependability
- Teamwork
- Problem-solving

- Communication
- Critical thinking
- Flexibility

LANGUAGES

- Azerbaijani & Turkish (Native)
- English (Full Professional Proficiency)

Russian(Elementary)